<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on JFREV</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on JFREV</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.151.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:09:05 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Marlboro Mega Iceblast 8</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_mega_iceblast_8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:09:05 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_mega_iceblast_8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After catching up with my old work colleague AV I made the conscious decision to take a walkdown to China town with a goal in mind to grab a quick snack (whic I had already decided on to be those Hong Kong Egg Waffles as they caught my eye the day before). While I was headed there I knew in the back of my mind I was going to try find a pack of the Marlboro DRYs I had been recommendedon Redbook. While I was unsuccessful to grab a pack I caved at the shop at bought the Marlboro Mega Iceblast out of pure curiosity. I knew I was going to grab these at some point just out of pure interest. I must say while the other Marlboros seem quite strong/rough I was very surprised by this one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marlboro Watermelon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_watermelon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:09:58 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_watermelon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another delightful pack I picked up during when I grabbed the Mevius Blueberries. I won&amp;rsquo;t bother repeat the origina story here since it can be found on the other post here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a look to see that these are originally from Argentina, much like the other Marlboros I find them quite harsh to begin with. Although the crush ball does release a wonderful smell the overall flavour while smoking them seems to fade pretty quick.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mevius Blueberry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/mevius_blueberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:09:58 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/mevius_blueberry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I actually went into a shop near uni (was there for dinner and catching up with a friend visiting from the US + other petrolheads) and whipped out my old ESSE pack asking if they had anything like them as a sign to show what I was after. I actually left once I was done eating while the others remained inside the resstaurant as the sign for the tobaccionist was staring at me right in the face and curiosity got the better of me lmao.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marlboro Iceblast</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_iceblast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:10:50 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_iceblast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A pack I grabbed for a wedding as I did not want to bring a pre-opened pack and risk not having enough for the night and to go around.
There is a nice cool sensation at the end of each puff but there is a strong after taste. More suited to a higher blood alcohol level than sober (then again I’m not one to smoke unless I am drinking anyway). No additional comments – will keep em around since there are plenty more left in the pack.
However part of me thinks it might actually take some time before I can go through all of them. It is also a design of a more dead social calendar too since there isn’t much appetite from my end to sit around at home and smoke.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>African Mola: Random Five</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/african_mola/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:10:44 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/african_mola/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These were initially a gift from a friend at a wedding, which he mentioned he had lying around (unsure about the time frame they spent in opened storage). After the ceremonies he told me to keep them. Quite interesting as the cigarettes all look largely similar from the outside but each has some sort of distinctive fruit related flavour after taste once smoked.
These are not particularly overwhelming on the tastebuds but leaves  your mouth feeling a little bit fresh rather than the regular ciggy after taste. Maybe I need to try a fresher pack  for better flavour but I think the true sentimentality behind these will always be:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchester Double Drive</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/manchester_doubledrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:10:48 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/manchester_doubledrive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These were the only other pack of darts I was able to procure along with the Esses prior to the bucks.
Like the Esses there will always be a fond memory associated with these, given how well received they were.
They are also the first with (recorded perhaps) time I can note where there were two pop capsules within the one dart.
I love the overall flavour and the sensation it leaves in the mouth which makes it bearable even if I am not completely smashed off my face. I’d classify this one as pretty dangerous in terms of actually smoking for the sake of smoking. All in all, from all the different darts I’ve tried to procure this one seems to be the most common one when asked for the international offerings that they have.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esse Change</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/esse_change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:10:40 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/esse_change/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These were one of original packs I was able to procure prior to a bucks. These along with the Manchesters. Given we were all piss drunk once we started craving that sweet hit of Nicotine these were received quite well and made me feel basically like a hero as we were otherwise durrie starved for that first night.
From the initial get go these darts are much smaller than your usual/regular types. What they lack in sizing they make up for in a nice cool/chill sensation as they are smoked. The only downside is these cigarettes burn through quick due to their smaller size (and hence reduced nicotine content).
Had a quick look around and on the internet and turns out that this cigarette is smaller and lighter as it is primarily marketed/directed towards women.
Would Smoke Again Rating (WSAR): Y
Pop Capsule: Y&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
