<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Marlboro on JFREV</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/marlboro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marlboro on JFREV</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.151.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:09:05 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/marlboro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Marlboro Mega Iceblast 8</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_mega_iceblast_8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:09:05 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_mega_iceblast_8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After catching up with my old work colleague AV I made the conscious decision to take a walkdown to China town with a goal in mind to grab a quick snack (whic I had already decided on to be those Hong Kong Egg Waffles as they caught my eye the day before). While I was headed there I knew in the back of my mind I was going to try find a pack of the Marlboro DRYs I had been recommendedon Redbook. While I was unsuccessful to grab a pack I caved at the shop at bought the Marlboro Mega Iceblast out of pure curiosity. I knew I was going to grab these at some point just out of pure interest. I must say while the other Marlboros seem quite strong/rough I was very surprised by this one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marlboro Watermelon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_watermelon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:09:58 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_watermelon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another delightful pack I picked up during when I grabbed the Mevius Blueberries. I won&amp;rsquo;t bother repeat the origina story here since it can be found on the other post here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a look to see that these are originally from Argentina, much like the other Marlboros I find them quite harsh to begin with. Although the crush ball does release a wonderful smell the overall flavour while smoking them seems to fade pretty quick.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marlboro Iceblast</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_iceblast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:10:50 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/marlboro_iceblast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A pack I grabbed for a wedding as I did not want to bring a pre-opened pack and risk not having enough for the night and to go around.
There is a nice cool sensation at the end of each puff but there is a strong after taste. More suited to a higher blood alcohol level than sober (then again I’m not one to smoke unless I am drinking anyway). No additional comments – will keep em around since there are plenty more left in the pack.
However part of me thinks it might actually take some time before I can go through all of them. It is also a design of a more dead social calendar too since there isn’t much appetite from my end to sit around at home and smoke.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
